http://flexkrete.com/terms-and-privacy/

Terms of Use
Website Terms and Conditions of Use
1. Terms
By accessing this website, you are agreeing to be bound by these website Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.
2. Use License
Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on FlexKRETE's website for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license, you may not:
modify or copy the materials;
use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on FlexKRETE's website;
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by FlexKRETE at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.
3. Disclaimer
The materials on FlexKRETE's web site are provided "as is". FlexKRETE makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, FlexKRETE does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
4. Limitations
In no event shall FlexKRETE or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on FlexKRETE's Internet site, even if FlexKRETE or a FlexKRETE authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
5. Revisions and Errata
The materials appearing on FlexKRETE's web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. FlexKRETE does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. FlexKRETE may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. FlexKRETE does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.
6. Links
FlexKRETE has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by FlexKRETE of the site. Use of any such linked website is at the user's own risk.
7. Site Terms of Use Modifications
FlexKRETE may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then-current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.
8. Governing Law
Any claim relating to FlexKRETE's web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Texas without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Subscribe Sign up to receive our 'How-to' Newsletter, Tips, Case Studies,
Video Tutorials and More!
Related
Eroded Concrete Spillway Repair
Eroded Concrete Spillway Repair: Once concrete dams and spillways begin breaking down, it rapidly deteriorates. Repairs on...
More
How to Repair Potholes Permanently
Potholes, potholes, potholes. Just fix them already. They ruin tires and wheels and never seem...
More
Multiple Depth Repair Mix Ratios
Bank parking lot entrance had repair depths from 1/2" to 5". Using the standard FlexKRETE mix...
More
Failed Repair: Bridge Sidewalk Repair
What an Ugly, Failed Repair. FlexKRETE handled this bridge/sidewalk repair - rusty rebar too. Jeff...
More
Concrete Barrier Repair: DFW Int’l Airport
We Keep Traffic Moving At DFW Int'l Airport. Dallas-Fort Worth International Airport is one of the world’s...
More
Hazard Repair and Decorative Coating
Severe Hazard Repair and Decorative Coating in Hours. Customer: United States Postal Service (USPS) Problem:...
More
Top 5 Videos and Case Studies
Here are 5 of Our Most Popular Videos. Creating and sharing new 'how-to' videos and...
More
Concrete Floor Repair: Trench Drain
This trench drain's spalling concrete and deterioration created a severe safety hazard. Shown in these before and after pictures, FlexKRETE...
More
DOT Road and Bridge: Concrete Repair
There's no shortage of DOT work contractors who use FlexKRETE - The One That Works....
More
Permanent Nose Median Repair
Concrete Curb Patching 101. The City of Plano, Texas was impressed. Problem: Broken nose medians from...
More
Pothole Repairs: DFW Int’l Airport
We Tackled DFW Int'l's Terminal A Bridge Pothole Repairs. And did it in a day,...
More
Flooring: Broadcast Over Tile
Flooring: Broadcast Over Tile  A 40-year-old hospital bathroom floor desperately needed replacement, but removing the tile was too time...
More
Increasing Yield On Deep Repairs
Yes, You Can Increase Yield On Deep Repair Jobs. Here's the case study. Contractor: Jeff Schubert,...
More
FlexKRETE’s Customized Training School
FlexKRETE's Customized Training School FlexKRETE Technologies has upgraded its popular school with the creation of...
More
Waterpark Support Column Repair
Structure safety is always a concern. Especially where children play. Deteriorating support columns with rusty rebar...
More
Texas DOT Joint Repair
On The Road with TxDOT for Joint Repairs. Joint repairs can be a challenging task...
More
Long-term Spalling Concrete Repair That’s Fast
Long-term Spalling Concrete Repair That's Fast: This large area of concrete spalls at a Lowe's...
More
TOP 5 Cold Weather APPLICATIONS
Winter Concrete Repair Is Big Money. Here's our TOP 5 Cold Weather Applications. With virtually no temperature restrictions,...
More
Testing FlexKrete’s Impact and Bond Strength
FlexKRETE Gets Tested. But this time, not by us. Don't just take our word for...
More
Concrete Lined Drainage Channel Repair
Concrete-lined Drainage Channels Can Be Repaired. And be ready to handle water in a few...
More
The $30,000 Trip Hazzard
Don't Get Sued Over 'Easy-to-Fix' Repairs. The $30,000 Trip Hazard. You don't have to look...
More
What Can You Repair With FlexKRETE?
FlexKRETE repairs potholes, spalls, cracks, joints, verticals, overheads and more: Instead of writing a bunch...
More
30 Concrete Repairs Using FlexKRETE
30 Concrete Repairs Using FlexKRETE: You may not realize it, but FlexKRETE is in use...
More
Use A Power Trowel To Apply FlexKrete
Power Trowel FlexKrete To Complete Projects Quickly & Smoothly. Permanently repairing large areas of damaged...
More
Doing it Right the First Time
Just Do it Right the First Time. It's the first step in being remarkable. Successful companies...
More
Concrete Steps Repair
Repairing Steps Has Never Been Easy - Until Now. CASE STUDY: Permanent Concrete Steps Repair...
More
Emergency Concrete Repair
Emergency Concrete Repair: Airports • C-Stores • Truck Stops • Docks • Drive-Thrus • Restaurants...
More
Damaged Sidewalks: Repair Now to Save Money Later
Damaged and uneven sidewalks can be hazardous and they're everywhere.  FlexKRETE makes it easy, cost-effective,...
More
Extreme Damage Calls For An Extreme Solution
Extreme Damage Calls For An Extreme Solution: The crushing brutality of daily forklift traffic can...
More
Concrete and Rebar: Bollard Pole Repair
Concrete and Rebar at DFW Airport. Bollard Pole repairs are hard unless you're using FlexKRETE....
More
Underground Garage Overhead Repair
Debris hung by a thread in this underground parking garage. Eliminating an immediate safety hazard...
More
Richardson Texas Street Overlay
Richardson, Texas Street Overlay: FlexKRETE helped expedite this large-scale project. Expanding streets and bridges and...
More
FlexKRETE Renews Vegas Fremont St. Experience
FlexKRETE Renews Vegas Fremont St. Experience: 35 million tourists trample the surface of Fremont Street...
More
Accelerate Large Jobs Using A Mortar Mixer
Accelerate Large Jobs Using A Mortar Mixer: For big jobs, using a mortar mixer is not...
More
Repairing Concrete Spalls Permanently
The Step-by-Step FlexKRETE Repair Method. CASE STUDY: Repairing Spalls Permanently  Customer: Lowes Home Improvement  Problem:...
More
FlexKRETE Digital FlipBook
Before and After Concrete Repair Images The almost-famous FlexKRETE Flipbook is now viewable online! Viewed hundreds...
More
24/7 Loading Dock Repaired in Hours, Not Days
24/7 Loading Dock Repaired in Hours, Not Days: Getting this loading dock repaired quickly was...
More
“This Is Why I’m Here” Is What We Hear Most at World of Concrete – WOC2018 Recap
"This Is Why I'm Here" Is What We Hear Most at World of Concrete -...
More
Pouring New Concrete Is Unnecessary
These before and after pictures are great examples of how quick, easy and profitable concrete...
More
Trowel-Down Using FlexKrete with Red Quartz
Trowel-Down Using FlexKrete with Red Quartz FlexKrete distributor Kelly Moore Paints helped solve a big...
More
View all posts by
SubscribeSign up to receive our 'How-to' Newsletter, Tips, Case Studies,
Video Tutorials and More!
